# KELSEY OSHIRO

• full stack software engineer •

# ABOUT ME

Bubbly and innovative software engineer specializing in front end technologies. Approaches challenges with a creative and design-driven, problem-solving mindset. Brings strong communication skills, a collaborative attitude, contagious positivity, and critical thinking from a background in



. . .

<u>LinkedIn</u>

kelsocode@gmail.com

kelseyoshiro.com

## EDUCATION

2020- 2021 • Flatiron School Full Stack Web Development, Ruby on Rails, JavaScript, React

2010-2014 • Colorado State University Bachelors of Science in Health and Exercise Science

# TECHNICAL SKILLS

Ruby on Rails, Javascript (ES6/ES2015), React, Styled Components, HTML5, CSS3, SQLite3, PostgreSQL, Git, React Router, Prismic

#### TECHNICAL PROJECTS

#### **Portfolio**

healthcare.

My personal portfolio website showcasing my work

- Utilized React and Styled Components to build this app
- Implemented EmailJS for the contact form
- Created a clean user interface with responsive design

#### Pokémon Team Builder

A web app designed for Pokémon trainers to help them build their perfect team

- Utilized React to create this app
- Designed a unique experience for users by applying dynamic styling for each type of Pokémon
- Used the PokéApi to supply data for this app

#### **Props**

A web app for plant lovers to advertise and trade their propagated houseplants

- Went beyond course curriculum and learned Python, Django, and Postgres, which were all technologies unfamiliar to me prior to this project
- Expanded on my new knowledge of Django and implemented Django REST Framework Simple jwt for the authentication feature of this app
- Designed the Props logo

### EXPERIENCE

#### 2015-2017, Boulder Community Health-Cardiac Rehabilitation

2018-2020 Exercise Physiologist

- Collaborated on a multidisciplinary team of nurses, respiratory therapists, and doctors to create care plans for patients who recently underwent open heart surgery and other cardiac procedures
- Interpreted complex EKG rhythms and used sophisticated equipment and software to capture and record this data

## 2017-2018 Walt Disney World Resort

Disney College Program Internship

- Created memorable vacations for guests while demonstrating critical problem solving and high quality listening when defusing guest situations
- Engaged in courses exploring the history of the Walt Disney Company and its core business values